

No-7, First Floor, Basaweshwara Nilaya, 5th Cross, 2nd Main, Brindavan Nagar, Chikkadugodi, Bangalore 560029 India

🛘 (+91) 8123089095 | 🗷 vikrant.biswas@gmail.com | 🏕 vikrant.pages.dev | 🖸 windlessstorm | 🛅 vikrantb

Summary

Currently Software Engineer at Unified Communication company Mitel Networks. 5+ years of experience specializing in Full Stack Development, Test Automation, and System Administration. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Skills

DevOps AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins

Back-end Express, Django, REST API Front-end Angular, React, Vue, Hugo

Programming Node.js, Typescript, Python, Rust, C

Work Experience _____

Mitel Networks Co. Bangalore, India

SOFTWARE ENGINEER Aug. 2017 - Present

- Built real-time collaborative whiteboard solution for our meeting platform.
- Built automated test framework, tests and CI/CD pipeline on Jenkins using Python, Selenium, Typescript, NodeJs.

Endurance International Group

Bangalore, India

HOSTING PRODUCT ENGINEER

Dec. 2016 - Aug. 2017

· Pro-actively monitor product/services/site performance, uptime, availability and analyze logs/metrics and recommend/contribute to fixes.

iSOKE Technologies Bangalore, India

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

- May. 2016 Aug. 2016 • Developed application to load test network appliances with simulated traffic of various L2, L3, and L4 network protocols.
- · Developed auto-scaling large-scale network traffic simulator, used to simulate mutiple network topology and state.

Honors & Awards

Feb. 2022 Finalist, Mitel Global Shark Tank Global, Remote Oct. 2021 1st Place, Mitel India Hackathon Bangalore, India feb. 2021 4th Place, Mitel Global Shark Tank Global, Remote Oct. 2020 1st Place, Mitel India Hackathon Bangalore, India

Education

MAKAUT (Maulana Abul Kalam Azad University of Technology)

Kolkata, India

B. TECH. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Aug. 2011 - Sept. 2015

· Participated in and won multiple coding competitions.

Extracurricular Activity

Advent of Code 2019 Bangalore, India

PARTICIPANT Dec. 2019

• Tried to learn Rust from basics while solving all the puzzles.

Advent of Code 2018 Bangalore, India

PARTICIPANT Dec. 2018

• Tried to learn Go-lang from basics while solving all the puzzles.

Advent of Code 2017 Bangalore, India

PARTICIPANT Dec. 2017

Had fun trying to do visualization for all the puzzle solutions in JavaScript

VIKRANT BISWAS · RÉSUMÉ **DECEMBER 12, 2022**